foreign
again it's um I tell people like to
drive
all the people the things that they want
and they they're doing these type of
things
and not really being aware of that a lot
of pain at all
and broadcast
the people
around
says do not take each other's money this
time
foreign
okay let's let's put this in the
perspective you said that God
's team
okay yeah you said you said garbage team
against me right
I'm saying like Okay like me and you and
I
um
say friends
or something like that and then I may
take the sky down with you don't get me
a primary gym or something or
um a propane or something like this but
then I might have told you that I needed
something to eat or something like that
and so to me that's being dishonest and
then also it's
um when I understand
oh
if I was expecting for something happens
you know
and I needed to get out
and I will pay the officials
you know like because I stole something
from the time to hurt somebody and then
I would say all the pictures to get out
of jail or practice let me get ideas
don't worry about those other people and
then they take it
and so I'm worried about
these other people not hearing me and
seeing me make this private a judge or
whomever where God is directly out of
both of us and we're welcome from no
trouble but most men you know people
serious don't think like that they think
that they're trying to hide
where God is looking at the thing on the
web because of those big families that
have been a lot of questions but that's
not understand
also to put this in uh in terms of
nothing to do a lot of things the 2013
you're very correct in that you go to
the market
and you buy things and then you will go
and get the
the uh
you give the cashier five dollars and
see things that you've over 20 dollars
so it gives you the change
you bought things for two dollars it
gives you 18 dollars back
because you thought you gave her money
though when you really gave her Piper
no you have two choices you can take the
18 and walk out
in which case you are eating other
people's money dishonest because at the
end of the day she'll count on money and
you'll be so 15.
oh you can give her the money back
the Toronto
the money back because you're only five
dollars
now when you accept God schemes it's
because if you do walk out of the money
you read other people's money
dishonestly
that person you don't make 15 dollars
you actually lose a lot more than the
15. something else will happen
where you lose
a lot of money
and on your way home you get a ticket
for 75 speeding ticket
or worse yet to get in an accident or
something
because breaking God's law is very
serious you know the seriousness here is
not just taking 15.50 is nothing but the
serious method is really disappointed
when when he says it's a commandment you
shall not beg each other's money
dishonest
so in that case
you return the money because God says
you will tell you
regardless of how much it is
right because they will cost you a lot
more
it cost you a lot more than than the
price of the sugars sometimes they
charge more numbers for
yeah
God never says War to the circus
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah you better you make sure that
you're objective rather than
aggressive because God makes it up to
you
so the Muslim is aware that when this
happens the people usually look at you
like my God you know there's some other
people around here they don't realize
that you return it because you're scared
to death
because it will actually cost you a lot
more because it was a lot smarter to
give back the money
so that's smarter a lot cheaper
and they make a lot more money than what
you learn away yes
[Music]
all right
because they belong to somebody who
worked very hard for them
I know some women
oh yeah
some people have a real struggle man
this is the real test yeah
okay bye-bye
okay okay
um yeah
they sent it to the head of the
Teamsters Union
was found detail trying to drive a
senator
give him a few acres of land in Las
Vegas
because because they wanted the senator
to
oppose deregulation of a trucking
industry which means the drivers make a
lot of money from you and me
in order to take other people's money
simply alone
so what the teams comes to the union
president wanted was to turn the
people's money simply unknown
because
attractive industry
and they made the trucking business
cheaper for us and less money for them
that's a prize
uh
[Music]
a way of life
yeah
if you don't drive it you cannot get
even in your own life
what what the price that you want a Visa
for example to hit the country and
right
but suppose to stay in the country means
they will kill you and Justice
is very difficult
yeah suppose
crime and your enemies in the government
are going to frame you and you know it
and you're given a chance to leave the
county but you have to leave let's say
100 good Egyptian pounds
if you do not give the 100 good Egyptian
pounds then you will allow other people
to commit also Injustice
and then if you die who will fit your
family or your children so it is a hard
question
I'm not putting myself in the festival I
don't need to so this is a theoretical
situation but this driver include when
you are asked
for payment for for say a policeman to
forget that you've done something wrong
like in the Philippines you know
for something new yeah I'm going to
forget
but my family lives
right
you don't understand anything with it
like going across the borders
is about right
here because he said he should not write
in order to take other people to my
husband right so we have the situations
in order to forget about the ticket now
what does the ticket money go to the
government Treasury
[Music]
where some other people are going to get
the money
possibly salaries or whatever so what
you're doing the diverting the money
from other stores but that is different
from the other case so suppose you want
to extradite your paper that's something
else you go again I take Egypt again
okay so you are not giving money to we
are not going to take away money from
the government government says You must
pay 10 pounds for
passport all right then you see this
hard-working man in Italian here is two
pounds hurry up
hurry up
he's gonna put my peppers on the side or
take your pepper and push it through so
my paper is going to be delayed
that's what happens you'll get priority
to your papers by pushing my paper on
the side or other people's purpose on
this side
that's true it will be at the expense of
other but before she says he would just
wake up early and walk work extra
on the top that's what they will do we
must remember that there is a lot of the
Quran that says if you are forced
by circumstance without being malicious
or deliberate then you are not
committing yourself
so God understands the circumstances
that if you don't get a Visa they will
kill you
self-defense your privacy
you are forced by circumstance and you
are not being malicious or deliberate
certainly not eating other people's
money in this honesty
of Common Sense Islam is absolutely
common sense
do you have a question
exactly
okay back to Latif
foreign
[Music]
definitely
okay
but just wait for it
um
okay they saying that you know my sister
might ask you about the moon
the feeling a lot of things to say
people take decided but trying to be
right before the people whatever you
know that's
they ask you Muhammad
about the presence of the moon so these
people really came to him saying you're
not a prophet
so instead of saying you're not a
prophet he said what what is the what
about the presence of the Moon
tell us about the presence of the Moon
but that's not the real question
the question is prove to us that you're
a prophet of God
so they're beating around the bush
okay but okay so God Is providing the
answers to Muhammad here in this verse
and tell them that this timing device
and it will tell us when to pass the
month which is the ninth month which is
the 12th month
we were looking at the moment today and
he said this is the second day of the
map
the new new number
you can tell by the fact that it starts
this early
bigger and bigger
until the full moon on the 14th
of the month so you can turn it's a
timing device
I'm not sure
to me okay what I'm sure of is that is
saying to me that people be
straightforward be happy the Mind first
believe that that's what it's saying to
me and that's what I teach but then I
have problems with that because
sometimes on Tuesday forward
so people tell me
and make feelings of whatever could hurt
that's very good you know cousin Society
say you should like maybe stare at each
other or whatever and you kind of hold
some of it but I'm not like that I'm
being straightforward because that means
what comes up comes out and it hurts
people's feelings and I don't mean to
hurt nobody's feelings you just to not
be straightforward it's you know booming
I don't like your hair I don't like you
know you know and I can say it and
because you know I haven't said to me
this person is hurt and then somebody
come back and tell me what you should
have said something that's a genius I've
heard they feel it just let me know and
then that kind of what's left on me
because maybe maybe I read it
okay
under any situation but
there are different ways of things that
are total there's a big remote required
it's doing it easy in mind for the Quran
says invite to the way of the Lord by
wisdom and check okay and being
diplomatic
yeah instead of saying I don't like your
hair you can say you know I like to help
better when it is up
well this is a positive
this is a positive statement at the same
time we told the person I don't like to
hear this way
but but you said it in a diplomatic way
your
straightforward
and you're telling the truth
but at the same time it didn't work
obviously
thank you
a little bit more we shall brighten the
crosses down again
but the United States
you may kill them if they attack you
[Laughter]
I actually
okay
correction correct I have to I have to
correct that she was trying to get Ahmed
wanted to track
got the shaving cream
cream
it was not
alone
[Music]
pillows
just put the pillow aside
what's the meaning of this
she had to explain that
[Laughter]
you shall fight on the cause of God
against also fight you
but do not aggress for God does not love
the aggressives
because you know Iraq attacked Iran
and they went on fighting each other
even in the second month months well
there is no war supposed to be no war
and then they claimed they're Muslims
the secret professor
rather
okay 191
[Music]
oppression is worse than Earth
do not find them at the sake of my
unless they attack you down in Advance
at you then you may kill them
and this would be their just retribution
keep going
Mercy
you may fight them to prevent oppression
and to practice God's religion and
complete freelance once every strange
there should be no aggression except
against the wicked
if they attack you during the safer
months then you may fight during the
second month and practice religious may
be left by equivalent responses if they
attack you you may attach them then
equivalent let's sufficient you shall
observe that and know that God is with
those to observe him and spirit is the
cause of God do not throw yourself with
your own words that you can pass it you
shall be charitable but God loves to
Canada
because that's really accepted changes
they
um
and talking about the um
but if somebody addressed us then you
can't fight them or tell them or even
get them to say you know amount of
punishment that they give us no more no
matter
do not accept only if they attack you
and really you don't blame the people
because of what the social Muslims do
but the Islam this is
because you do not attack until they
attack you
know how much uh
there was no war
when they went to North Africa it was
more war
you didn't agree and then when they went
to
spend the rest that's why they lost
experience
now when they went to Spain they went
for other reasons besides I think
they've been a lot of people they found
some resistance
foreign
Republican
so as you see the person is very clear
detect the side of the week but the the
instances where you fight is of two
seconds if you are attacked
all of you are oppressed
because the most precious thing
the most precious thing to us is our
convictions worshiping God Alone
if there's any circumstance that will
stop us from doing this you have to
fight to preserve it
you know you destroyed Mike yeah
no they may have to drink alone
we're talking about religious operation
what before I close before we Applause
I want to mention that uh
the record would be I was going to pray
in the morning at six o'clock and it is
followed by the Arabic language lessons
and we are having a lot of fun I'm
telling you
you're missing a lot of fun and the
students can testify to that also we
have the best Arabic course in the whole
world
just think next week the thief will be
reading Quran
it's right and she started she started
from zero
this morning we're gonna finish the
alphabet at the cursive
Quran
so a week from today I promise you but
if we're doing it
and this is how good the Arabic enforces
that's your heart yes this is the Quran
so a week from today inshallah the
people will be reading the Quran
yes
this is only two weeks
but when you read the word the Quran in
Arabic you understand what it is
no
yeah
and then we'll go home and sleep and
come back at six o'clock
what is that on
um
foreign
now I would say those are the
unperceivable
foreign
practices
you know there's a reason for them God
gave us a prescription
I'm sure all these things the casting is
a form of something called
the suffering business
and it is worship at the same time and
therefore I'm sorry twice
so we do it hoping that this will clean
our River but the idea that
you're out
I mean it's not it's not really about to
happen because if we think of it this
way as a commonly believe
it's a very simple Act of disobedience
if the verse also says that it is
29 which he means
if it is uh
any demands for remembering that which
is even greater so so if it's the mean
for remembering Allah we can also say
that Salat is a technique
foreign
how many common people think of God you
know
how often do they think oh God they wake
up in the morning and they're going to
work
foreign
right now just look at it
you like to do anything it says all your
whole beliefs Beware of God and let each
of your examine what he or she has
advanced for the coming days we shall
observe to God so God is consciousness
of everything you do do not be like
those who forgot that so he doesn't
forget because also
this is
not equal and those who have deserved
him and also represent Heaven both of
the girls in heaven are the women so it
says when people forget God God bless
them forget themselves because they
neglect themselves
and who who is the turn and searches
their soul they forget to repeat their
soul
a lot of people are very careful in the
morning to get a cup of tea or breakfast
so they're giving their body
there are a couple of coffee or
for breakfast
and the children
so they don't forget about it which is
not them
the body the Garment worn by them can
try for a blink of an eye
this whole life is quite a bit of an eye
here in contact
because and real life of the Hereafter
we'll be talking in terms of millions of
years so what is 60 degrees for 100
years
yet people put all the concentration of
this drink overnight and they're going
to be read before
skin
yeah
they are concentrating all the efforts
when it's really not important at all to
be full of thought man the woman try to
stay
beautiful Rodney it's not until it
doesn't matter
going on
what matters
this blink of an eye is very important
and that It prepares
so our goal is to go out in this life
is our sins also another way
watching our scene
foreign
questions
well if you feel kind of love you
I don't go for questions I was outside
otherwise no
for the tradition of Monday and
Thursdays Monday or Tuesday
you're not good
but fasting the number of days in issues
right
but if you break it off you have to pass
three days
are
it's all uh
obligatory they said in the Quran but uh
so if you fasted all of Ramadan if you
have no plans to do if you want to thank
you
you got to assess the specific number of
days
so Satan wants you to distribute that in
any way or form
so if you want to fast go on a diet in
other words forget reasons I will
deliberately break my chest I will go on
a diet and they will hit the base
foreign
the theft is righteous then I don't
understand it's just like well God says
in the Quran to do the five prayers and
I don't I don't feel that he did more
than five to get extra prayers
I mean they're not doing it just to yeah
well if he's doing this because you feel
like doing it that's the difference but
Ron says that the Quran says become very
extra pleasure because
that's that's what the difference is
that a sort of extra player the concerns
God says do them
they get up and deliver the light and
pray
but there are no limitations no specific
numbers and you have to do it because
you feel like it
and you are The Wanted for that so the
Quran being specific to this and says go
ahead and do extra Salah what never says
doors it says a specific number of days
right as far as fasting says passed a
specific number of days
for five days
right good
you're just making a problem I'm exactly
the same I think this is
what
so I'm gonna quit smoking
let's do that I'm gonna do it more
and then ready to drop
foreign
girlfriend
because God's merciful symbology don't
get like more credit for critique
yeah
when you do a good deal
when you do a bad bit it's supposed to
have one sin
yep
yeah
one good word and I'll give you rewards
for 10. but if you do a bad word you
will be punished for what so you have to
pay in policy to commit if you go drink
now for example
you have to pay for for the one of
friends
because you know it is wrong
but if you will be the hungry person on
the street
we lived a lot for feeding ten
when you do once a lot it's equivalent
to 10.
to get their loss
so
they uh the only unforgivable expenses
foreign
so like I mentioned this before
yeah and I stay away from
do I get anything extra for that I don't
know it sounds like a hobby for me I
forget it is you prevented the minus
from going into your record what you
want to know is just have yourself
this is
lots of things
I have to think about it but we do get
credit for that because we're passing
another point
foreign
here's the best let's look at it
okay 3570
25 7-0